Well, opolescence, what did you think of
our rehearsal?
>> What the is that? A cat.
>> That was awesome. This is seriously the
most fun I've had in like forever.
>> Yeah. A month ago, I didn't even know
how to hold drumsticks because I'm a
horse. Now I'm a pro. Every pony, shut
up. I'm getting a call. Answer it. Maybe
they need a drummer.
>> Hello. Wait, really? No, absolutely.
We'd love to.
>> Who is that?
>> Girls, I'm happy to announce we just
found our first gig.
>> The Lord has provided. I knew accepting
Jesus into my heart would pay off
eventually.
>> You see, I told you we were marvelous
darlings. They must have heard our demo
online.
>> I can't believe it. Where are we
playing? Manhattan Canterlot.
>> Princess Celestia's cruise ship. It will
be sailing across the Atlantic Ocean
this Friday.
>> Oh my. The SS Celestia. That's a luxury
cruise. Darling, do you know how many
influential ponies vacation on
Celestia's cruise? This could launch an
entire music career.
>> There's just one condition. They only
want us if if Starlight doesn't play.
Oh, well, she's out then.
>> Oh, that's okay. I've only been playing
for like a month. Obviously, they want
professionals.
>> Yeah, like me. We are still going,
right, [__] It's Princess Celestia's
cruise. Ponies spend years trying to get
opportunities like this.
>> Starlight comes with us. They only said
she couldn't perform.
>> Yeah, you'd be crazy to turn that down
because of me. I wasn't really into
drumming anyway. I mostly joined because
you three looked like you were having
fun. So, this is great actually.
>> Wow, look at the size of that thing.
>> Oh my, what a magnificent vessel.
>> Another reminder of God's incredible
creation.
>> Yes, and with plenty to do aboard, it is
a pity you'll only be carrying luggage,
[__]
>> What's that supposed to mean?
>> Oh, I'm just reminding Glim Glam of her
place, Flutter Titties. After all, she
isn't part of our glorious band, The
Marvelous Darlings.
>> Haha. Yeah,
>> though I do suppose every successful
band needs some pony to carry their
[__] So at least she won't totally be
useless baggage.
>> You call my girlfriend useless one more
time and you will be swimming with the
fishes.
>> Marionette, stop it.
>> Suck my balls, [__] She called
Starlight useless 237 times in the past
10 minutes, and I am sick of it. I know,
and I was tempted to intervene myself.
But then I remember what Jesus taught
us. We forgive thine enemy, and if they
refuse to repent, we let God deal with
them.
>> Oh, pish posh, darling. It's already
left my mind. Although, I must say,
there's still one minor issue that needs
taken care of.
>> What's that?
>> Celestia never gave us complimentary
rooms. Wherever shall we rest before we
go up on stage?
>> I can take care of that for us. You
girls wait here.
God damn. Put some honey on those
biscuits.
Hey, who keeps banging on my door? Haha.
It's probably some tick tockers trying
to get a rise out of me. You kids are
such silly little rascals.
Try it again and see what happens. When
I catch you, I'll drop my pants and
well, let's just say you really won't
like what happens next.
You [__] You trying to kill me? Stop
it.
God damn it. Just kill me already.
>> Hey, pull me back up right now before I
call the cops.
>> Wow, Mary, that that was just wow. But
you forgot one little thing.
Ow! What was that for? Your DNA is all
over the room. Now you have a defense
alibi. Your DNA is in the room now, too,
you idiot. Okay, fine. Do it just like I
taught you. To the side and not too
deep. Oh, what the [__]
>> I'm bored.
>> Me, too. You want to go kill some more
people before the show starts?
>> Okay, [__] Are you ready to do it?
>> Oh, you know it, honey. Just let me go
put on something a little more sexy.
>> Why? We're horses.
>> Starlight, a little help here.
You stole both of my kills. I didn't
even get to do anything. Look, I had to
act fast because I thought I heard
Fluttershy at the door. Besides, I tried
leaving one of them for you, but they
made it incredibly difficult to keep
alive. Oh, suck my balls, [__] You
knew exactly what you were doing.
>> Mommy, daddy, would you like to hear
about our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ?
Oh my goodness, Daddy. It's not too late
to repent for your sins and reach
heaven.
>> No, Fluttershy. Heaven isn't an option
for me.
>> Heaven is an option for any pony that
lets Jesus into their heart.
>> No, Fluttershy. You don't understand. I
am an atheist because what kind of God
would create a family as ugly as ours.
The Bible also says animals don't go to
heaven and we are horses. God will
probably stop me at the pearly gates
because I am a horse. So, no Fluttershy.
I will not pray. Instead, I will proudly
turn my back towards God and walk
straight into the fires of hell just to
prove that I have free will. Screw God.
>> Screw God. Screw God. No, Dad. Screw
you.
>> Holy [__] He dead.
>> Burn in hell. You sick son of a biscuit.
You know, the more I think about this,
the more I think we're making a really
dangerous mistake with this whole candy
making idea. How so? We're down below in
a cruise ship's basement making a
product that's illegal to sell in a
market that's already controlled by
Pinkie Pie. You're right. I'm serious.
Sparkle, I know you got this massive
hard on to break bad, but Pinkie Pie
owns the candy market. She's got
suppliers, customers, delivery routes,
connections. She knows every pony who
buys this stuff. What do we got compared
to that?
>> The scientific know how to make better
candy than anything she could make
herself.
>> And what happens if she finds out we're
selling it behind her back?
>> She'll be real mad.
>> Twilight, we're talking about getting on
the wrong side of the biggest candy
dealer in Equestria here. That's exactly
why we don't compete with Pinky. We'll
work with her and convince her to become
our partners with this.
>> Holy [__] it's yellow. Like actually
piss yellow and not that shitty food
coloring you see in cheap candy stores.
Twilight, this is a work of art.
>> It's nothing special. Just simple
science and crystallization is all one
needs to achieve a batch of sugar gems
like this.
>> I don't give a [__] what you call it.
Ponies are going to see this and lose
their minds when they see this. It's the
kind of [__] some rich [__] would pay
200 bits for just because some pony told
him he wasn't supposed to have it. Now
you're getting it.
>> I have to admit, you two have made an
interesting proposal, but I'm still
trying to figure out why I shouldn't
simply throw you two off this boat and
take your product for myself.
>> Because then you would only have one
shipment and you'd have no way of
getting another. You're assuming I would
want another. It's the same color as PP.
It will be hard sell in the market.
>> Hey, Pinkie Pie Trust. Shit's the bomb.
Yo,
>> now let's talk numbers.
>> $15,000 per pound. You receive 20% of
every sale.
>> So, what would I get? $2 million.
>> No. 3,000 is 15% of 15,000.
>> Oh, okay. No, thank you. Then
>> come on, Pinkie Pie. I think you're too
intelligent to pass up an opportunity
simply like this.
>> You're right. Which is why I will be
taking your product by force and killing
you.
>> Then make it yourself.
>> I can learn.
>> You could, but I'd imagine you'd spend a
great deal of time trying.
>> 80%.
>> 50.
>> 75%.
And I want control of distribution.
Also, you two manufacture the product. I
find the buyers, arrange the sales, and
assume the risk associated with moving
it, and you get to walk out of here
alive.
Sounds like a fair deal if you ask me.
>> 25%, so then that means we would get
>> $16 trillion.
>> Actually, 3,750.
>> Oh, okay.
>> The deal is settled. Now get out of
Pinkie Pie's secret office.
>> Mr. Kicks, I was still talking to them.
Why did you have to go and do that?
>> I was only trying to intimidate them.
>> No, you were speaking for me and that
makes me really mad.
>> Let's call it Pinkie Pie. Everything's
fine.
>> No, he ruined everything.
Mr. Pigs, please jump in the hole and un
alive yourself.
>> Pinkie Pie, please. We don't have to do
this. Jump in the hole or I'm going to
run alive your whole family.
>> No. No, I won't. I've seen your ways,
Pinky. I know what you are. And whether
I jump in this hole or not, you would
just kill my family regardless.
Holy [__] We just made a deal with
Pinkie Pie. Are we insane?
>> [__] [__] [__] We better get started
on the next batch before we end up like
Mr. Cakes. I'm bored. Well, the show
isn't until later tonight. We can like
go attack some more passengers if you're
up to it.
>> Hey, I've got an idea. So, there's this
new spell I've been studying that lets
you watch the memories of an inanimate
objects owner. Why don't we try it on
your dad's old hat and see him beat up
your mom? Why would that be fun?
>> You know, to reinvigorate your hate for
that man.
>> Yeah, I guess we can do that.
Damn it, Spectacle. Don't you ever get
tired of getting your [__] kicked in?
>> I'm just not good at fighting jackpot.
You know that about me.
>> [__] sis. We're unicorns. You could
throw half the damn town through a wall
if you really wanted to.
>> I don't want to hurt anyone. Sorry,
Jack.
>> Why the hell are you apologizing to me
for?
>> I don't know.
>> God, that's what pisses me off. They
beat the crap out of you and somehow
you're the one apologizing. Thanks again
for chasing those guys off, bro.
>> Yeah, well, some pony had to.
>> It's just whenever I use magic, I feel
so exhausted.
>> Me personally, I'd rather wake up
exhausted than let ponies stomp all over
me.
>> That's strange.
>> Yeah, I didn't know your parents were
brother and sister. No, I mean how it
almost looked like he was concerned for
her well-being.
>> He was probably only acting nice to get
something out of her. You know how men
are. Yeah, maybe. But what about
Hold that thought, [__] Something more
important just came up.
Starite, you don't got to do this.
Silence, Marionette. Rarity was mean to
speak the truth about me and my drumming
skills. And I have decided that I
deserve revenge. I'm just saying you
didn't have to call me useless.
>> Darling, are we seriously doing this
right now?
>> Rarity, what you said was kind of rude.
Maybe you should apologize.
>> No, I'm tired of pretending. Princess
Celestia staff made the correct decision
hiring us without her. We are here to
perform. Starlight is solely here
because Marionette insisted.
You think you're better than me
>> with that chopped weave, darling. A
puffer fish looks better than you and
them [__] is fat.
>> You [__]
>> Opolescence. Help me.
>> Oh my god, Starlight, you killed her.
>> No, the freezing cold waters of the
Antarctic killed her. You cannot pin
this on me. What are we going to tell
Celestia if she asks where Rarity is? We
tell her the truth that Rarity
accidentally fell overboard.
But you pushed her.
>> Twilight Pinkie Pie sold the whole pound
of candy and sent over our first
payment.
>> Pour it on that poop.
You said 20%. Where's the rest of the
$3,448?
>> I didn't do anything with it.
>> I see. If it wasn't you, then it seems
like we need to have ourselves a little
word with good old Pinkie Pie.
Yo, how's it looking up there? All
clear.
Damn, Sparkle. I know you want to break
bad, but do you really got to break
wind, too?
All right, Pinky. Where's our money?
>> Oh, hi, Twilight.
>> Don't you hire us. Give us our money.
>> Oh, golly. You two really don't
understand how any of this works, do
you?
>> We understand exactly how it works. You
sold our product and then you kept the
money for yourself. Is this really how a
business lady conducts business?
>> No. I sold your product and then I paid
everyone who helped sell it using both
of our cuts.
I have guys who move the product. Those
guys have guys who move the product.
Those guys have guys who actually sell
it. And every single one of them gets a
share.
>> That That's not what we agreed on. Yeah,
we agreed to 25%.
>> And we also agreed that I handled
distribution by paying the people who
made the sale possible.
>> What is this? This is our way of telling
you two to get something through your
skulls. Pinkie Pie is the only kingpin
in the country when it comes to candy.
>> You two girls make a very good product,
but I control where the candy goes. I am
the only reason your product is able to
reach the market at all. So trust me
when I say you need me a whole lot more
than I need you.
If you want to keep doing business with
me, I'll keep doing business with you.
>> You're a [__] We're not working with
you anymore.
>> If you have haters, it probably means
you're doing something right.
>> Hey, Mary, come join me for a drink.
>> You know I don't drink.
>> You're acting weird. Do you want to look
at your dad's memories again?
>> I'm only curious.
>> Okay, fine. But we're totally hitting
the jacuzzi after.
>> It's beautiful.
>> Yeah, it kind of is.
>> If the ferris wheel fell over, do you
think everyone would die?
>> Probably. Yeah.
>> Hey, bro. I know you'd rather be hanging
out with your friends at the quarry, but
thanks for coming with me to Six Flags
today.
>> Yeah. Well, you practically dragged me
here.
>> I wish today wouldn't end.
>> Me, too.
>> Jackpot.
>> Yeah.
>> Can I tell you something?
>> Depends. Is it weird?
>> Probably.
>> Go for it.
>> You're the most important pony in my
life. I know I'm always causing trouble
for you, but it's like no matter what
happens, you're always there for me. I
don't think I'd be able to smile anymore
if I didn't have you.
Okay, don't get all mushy. You're making
this really awkward.
>> Sorry.
>> And for the last time, stop apologizing.
But you're my favorite pony, too. I
guess it's only because I don't have
time to hang out with anybody else. I'm
too busy protecting your sorry ass. So,
like, yeah, congratulations. You're my
favorite by default.
>> I'll take it. Thanks, Jackpot.
I still can't believe you won this for
me.
>> One is a strong word, sis. They only
gave that to us out of pity. I wasted 15
bits on that thing.
>> Yeah, but that's what makes it mean so
much more.
Back, what's going on? Why are there
police outside our house?
>> I don't know. It's rare to see something
like this in a predominantly unicorn
neighborhood. Wait here, spectacle. I'm
going to go check what's wrong.
>> You can't go in there.
>> This is my house. What's going on?
>> Look, son. I don't know how to tell you
this.
>> Where's our parents? Where's our mommy
and daddy?
>> Look, kid. There was a breakin and your
parents tried to fight off the attacker,
but God, they were weak little [__]
and got shot to death. But if you want,
I could be your new daddy.
What do we do now, Jack?
>> I don't know. All of our family's money
was in that house, and we can't even go
inside because it's a crime scene.
>> Then where will we sleep? Are we just
going to be homeless from now on? I want
to go home.
>> We'll figure something out, sis. Come
on. Let's get out of the rain first and
then we'll go over to the Motel 6, which
is the worst hotel on Earth, but somehow
the best hotel in Equestria, right
behind the Best Western with two and a
half stars.
Looks like no one's here. Can't say I'm
all that surprised since this place has
two and a half stars. Maybe we should
wait.
>> Rather not. This is Ponyville, so we'd
most likely run into some crack addicts.
Spectacle. Use your magic to break one
of the locks to a motel room.
>> I can't. That would be breaking and
entering. Mommy and daddy says that's
bad.
>> We don't have a mommy or daddy anymore.
God dang it. This is exactly when you're
supposed to use magic. If there was ever
a time to stop holding yourself back,
it's tonight.
>> I'll try.
>> I'm sorry, Jack. I just can't. Not with
my unicile dysfunction.
>> Fine, stand back. I'll just do it myself
then.
>> Thank you for coming.
>> Look, no offense, but if this is another
one of those we're doing the best we can
bits, just speed it up. We don't really
have time for this.
>> What?
>> Sorry. We just haven't been sleeping
much these days. Well, you'll be happy
to learn that we butt cracked open a
major breakthrough in the case. Turns
out it wasn't just simple burglary
attempt after all. Do you two kids know
this sexy man?
>> Jack, that's the guy who works at the
Six Flags down the road.
>> Yeah, the one whose massive booty cheeks
clap like an atom bomb when he moves
around. He gave me the teddy bear. But
why would he be a suspect?
>> We think he's the one who broke into
your house and made your parents his
[__] by killing them. A flock camera
captured this just before the killings
where he is shown crouched down behind a
bush with a massive pair of stinky butt
cheeks. Now, don't worry. His pants
wasn't down for any weird reasons. It's
just that his butt crack is so big the
skinny jean simply couldn't contain all
that ass.
>> Jack, what are you planning on doing?
>> I'm going to find the son of a [__] and
kill him.
>> Jack, you can't. He killed mom and dad
and he'll kill you, too.
>> Spectacle. You heard what the police at
the station said. None of the money was
stolen. Don't you know what that means?
He was after you. He was trying to take
you
>> then. Then let's just go. We'll hop on a
bus and leave this town forever and
start a new life somewhere else,
somewhere safe.
>> So, he just gets away with it.
>> No, we let the police do their job. And
he gets arrested like the law says.
>> I'm sorry, sis, but that just doesn't
sit right with me. The police installed
flock cameras and they don't even use
them to solve crimes. They had the
footage for months so they could check
out his fat cheeks and nothing more.
They only told us out of formality. This
man has to die tonight and it's going to
be done by my own two hooves.
I should have been cautious from you
from the start. No one who goes to Six
Flags can be totally sane.
Now to see what you're hiding, you sick
freak.
Oh, dear God. It's worse than any of us
could have ever imagined.
>> Took you long enough. That's right,
Jackpot. I've been watching you as you
came to Six Flags for years, and now I
finally have you right where I want you.
>> Spectacle. Spectacle, are you there?
>> Yeah, I'm having dinner. Some guy threw
a whole slice of pizza away. Can you
believe it? Spectacle, call the cops.
He's not just some kidnapper murderer.
He's worse. He's gay.
>> Okay. Do you want me to save you a
pepperoni?
>> Step away from the cult. And put your
hands in the air.
>> Oh [__] It's my daddy.
>> Son, no one has to die here tonight.
Just put the Yahi paddle down.
>> What? Are you going to shoot your own
son? Like total homophobe alert.
>> Unfortunately, I just might have to. Not
because you killed two people, but
because you are a part of the deadly
[__] regime that is killing this
Christian nation.
>> But dad, aren't you on the registry,
too?
>> That's different because I am a cop, so
the laws don't apply to me. I knew you
were a lost cause when you stole my
Crunchyroll subscription to watch Taog
out focus. You could have been one of
those cool gays that listen to good gay
people music like Marina and the
Diamonds or Madonna. But no, you just
have to listen to Chapel Ran and Taylor
Swift, you sick, Swifty bastard. If I
kill you, I will return to the police
station as an American hero.
>> Well, do it then if you got the big
balls. But I know you won't, Dad,
because you're a weak ass [__] That's
why mom left you. Because you're
pathetic.
>> Your mother died from cancer, you dumb
[__]
>> Yeah, well, I don't give a [__] Now,
listen up, daddy, because I'm going to
tell you how this is going to play out.
You're going to stand there for the next
10 minutes crying like a little [__]
while I walk out that door to hit up the
new Chappelle Ran concert. You got it?
Wow, that's strange. He really seemed to
care a whole lot about her. He was
probably only pretending to be nice to
her to get something. Yeah, maybe you're
right.
>> Attention guests, this is your goddess,
Princess Celestia. Will every pony
please gather in the main hall for a
very important announcement?
What's happening?
>> I don't know. This can't be because of
rarity, could it?
>> I have some terrible news to deliver, My
Little Ponies. Due to unforeseen
circumstances, most of you will die
tonight. But more importantly, tonight's
musical performance has been cancelled.
>> Hell yeah. Suck it, Rarity. Earlier this
evening, one of our passengers who was
of the Pony Master race, aka a unicorn,
accidentally fell overboard. The ship,
otherwise known as the SS Celestia,
which is named after me specifically,
has sustained heavy damage when her
horns scraped the side of the ship.
>> Holy [__] we caused this.
>> Our engineers estimate we have
approximately 2 hours before the ship is
completely underwater. Yes, Fluttershy.
>> Where are the lifeboats?
>> Fear not, for I have one lifeboat
exclusively for me. So my reign shall
carry on.
>> But we in the middle of the Atlantic
Ocean.
>> Yes, I am aware of the obvious fact and
I am frankly confused as to why you are
saying such an obvious thing.
>> Don't you have an evacuation plan?
>> Princess Luna says as normal ponies and
not alicorns, you are all expendable.
Luna says, "Also, any passenger who
successfully makes it back to land alive
will receive a complimentary 20% off
coupon for next week's cruise. I think
I'm going to fly home to get help,
right?" No, probably not. It'll take me
way more than 2 hours. So, you'll be
frozen to death with the rest of the
unicorns and earth ponies by the time I
even reach the mainland. But I will pray
for you. Hallelujah. Thank the Lord.
Amen.
Starlight, come back. Where the dick are
you going?
>> It's not over yet. We can still have
fun.
>> Starlight, the cruise is over.
>> I know.
>> We're stranded in the middle of the
Atlantic. So, forget the gig. We're not
going to be famous now. We have bigger
problems than that.
Star, I never cared about that stupid
music gig. Okay. I only came because I
thought it'd be fun to spend a couple of
days with you. Just like, you know,
being super gay girlfriends on a fancy
cruise ship.
>> Is that true?
>> My music sucked major balls. I know
that. I I only pretended to care about
the gig stuff so we could hang out. I
know. You probably think I'm some dumb
cringe loser now, huh?
>> Hey girls, I managed to climb back on
board with my mighty unicorn magic and
they fixed the leak. Now the ship isn't
sinking anymore.
>> This is Princess Celestia to let every
pony know that the ship is still in fact
sinking and it's sinking even faster.
Y'all [__] going to die.
>> Starlight, let's go. We have to make
like a tree and leaf.
>> Mary. Oh my god. Mary, are you all
right?
Ew.
History will remember this day, Luna.
Not for the tragedy itself, but because
of my incredible leadership. Years from
now, ponies will tell stories and sing
their praises how the great Princess
Celestia, the ruler who stood strong as
her magnificent cruise ship sank. Why,
you weren't on the ship.
>> Yes, but I was still monitoring the
situation from another boat at a safe
distance. With proper word play and
history books, we can make people think
I stayed aboard a ship until the very
end. What if ponies ask which boat?
>> We ostracize anyone who dares to seek
the truth like they do with World War
II. We will call this day Celestia Day.
>> You're naming it after yourself?
>> No, I'm naming it after my ship.
>> I don't know. It sounds a little
egotistical.
>> I've got it. We shall call this day 911
because that was the time the ship began
to sink.
>> Well, at least it wasn't at 6:07.
Don't you worry, Mary. I'm going to get
us home. I'll swim all the way back to
Ponyville. All 300 miles.
>> Starlight, what are you doing?
>> I'm swimming back to Ponyville.
>> But you've been doggy paddling for hours
and the ship is still right there. How
are you going to make it?
>> Okay, so maybe it's a little bit farther
than I thought, but I can't just give
up. Marionette's life is depending on
me. Star.
>> Mary, Starlight, where are we?
>> Funny story. So, the ship's going down
and now we're in the Atlantic Ocean. But
it's totally fine because I'm going to
swim us home.
>> We're in the water and your plan is to
swim all the way home with me on your
back.
>> Yeah, horrible plan. I know,
>> Pooky. That's the most idiotic romantic
gesture I have ever heard. I'm going to
reward you with so much sex when we get
home.
Looks, some speedboats are coming.
They've come to rescue us.
>> Hey, do you guys need some help? Oh,
never mind. It's just some unicorns. Oh,
no. Racist Earth ponies.
>> You still have the hat?
>> I couldn't just leave it, you know. It's
a trophy. I suppose. And you want to see
the rest of your parents' memories,
don't you? I guess I owe you that much
for this mess. I got us in.
>> No, I don't blame you. But I do want to
see them if you wouldn't mind using that
magic just one more time.
You know, I'm always incredibly
surprised how they managed to sneak
Tinky Winkies fat Teletubby ass past
that ESRB rating system. Like, what's
the point of a rating system if they
ain't even going to follow their own
rules?
Jackpot. Do you ever think about how
different things could have been?
>> Like if our parents didn't get murdered
by some psychopath when we were kids.
Yeah. All the time.
>> We've lost so much. But no matter what,
we always had each other. Even when it
felt like the whole world around us was
falling apart. When you really think
about it, we don't need anyone else, do
we?
Well, I can't say I know people besides
us who share the same excitement for
studying the extensive lore of the
Teletubbies.
>> Yeah, we really don't need anyone else.
>> Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
Jack, I think I think I might be
pregnant.
>> Okay,
>> that's all you have to say? We're going
to have a family in 9 months and all you
have to say is okay.
>> Can't we just like leave it behind the
Arby's dumpster or something?
>> Congratulations. Your wife gave birth to
two healthy twins.
>> No [__] Twins? Damn, we got the deluxe
package. Well, at least they look more
like me than you, Spectacle. If they
were ugly as you, that would have sucked
so much balls.
Damn, they just latch on to each other
like amiebas. I don't like the one on
the left. It looks like it wants to kick
me in the balls.
>> Jack, be nice. Trixie is only 3 hours
old.
>> Exactly. That's too early to be acting
like a [__]
>> Unfortunately, we'll have to keep
Marionette in hospice care for the time
being.
>> Why? What's wrong with her?
>> Hard to say. She's biologically a
unicorn, but she doesn't have a horn.
Without one, she won't be able to
channel magic, so she's physically weak.
It will be a rough road ahead for her,
but with the right medicine, she'll
survive.
>> And Trixie,
>> well, Trixie is free to go home with you
now. In fact, the little rascal is quite
powerful for a newborn. I would keep an
eye on Trixie if I were you to make sure
no mischief happens.
>> Hell yeah. I knew I like this [__] for
a reason. Here comes the choo choo
train.
>> No, the cute and funny Trixie doesn't
want banana and cream oatmeal. Father,
Trixie wants a can of Spaghettiio O's.
>> Did our baby just make demands?
>> Yeah, I think so.
>> Did you not hear Trixie before? Trixie
wants Chef Boyardd Spaghettiio's. I
heard you the first time, [__] I'm
just wondering why it is that a
3-month-old would make such demands at
its own father.
>> Because your job is to feed Trixie. If
Trixie does not get what Trixie wants,
the great and powerful Trixie will
refuse to eat and Trixie will die. And
then Trixiey's blood will be on your
hands and you will be placed in cuffs
and thusly taken to a prison
institution.
The ball is in your court now, father.
You've been under a lot of stress. Is it
about Marionette?
>> Nah, it's the other one with the big ass
purple witch hat. It's only a year and a
half and it's acting like it's the ruler
of the universe.
>> Trixie is still a baby. That's fairly
normal for a pony of their age.
>> No, you don't understand. Trixie has a
better magic output than most adult
unicorns. It's literally impossible to
say no to it because it would shoot you
with a gun.
>> I noticed you call Trixie an it.
>> I refuse to acknowledge it as a living
creature because it scares me. Jack, we
need to talk about something we
discovered. Trixiey's magic isn't
exactly just developing normally. We
think because Trixie is tied so strongly
to them, Marionette and Spectacle,
Trixie is absorbing their magic.
>> Are you saying she's killing them?
>> We think it's because Spectacle made it
a habit to avoid using magic at all cost
that it left an ungodly amount for her
kids. You also say Marionette is
struggling to walk. That's because
unicorn bodies are naturally more
fragile than earth ponies or pegasy.
They rely on the strength of their own
magic. Marionette's body can't grow in
that kind of environment. Then what do
we do?
Hey, sorry I haven't visited in a while.
I've been dealing with a load of [__]
lately. I had to talk to the doctors
again. I know how much you were against
the idea, but Trixie and Marionette
can't stay together. Apparently
Trixiey's magic is still siphoning hers
and she's still getting weaker.
I've decided that I'm going to take
Marionette. God, she's she's getting so
small, but she's hanging in there. I
think it's because you gave her so much
love while you were around. But she
still needs constant monitoring and
there's no way some random orphanage is
going to do that. I'll tell her you and
Trixie had to go somewhere and you'll
come back eventually. I don't know if
I'm doing the right thing, but honestly,
I don't really care anymore. Losing
family isn't something new to me.
Opolescence, you've come to rescue mama.
>> You jumped overboard, destroying one of
your own nine lives to save mine.
You fought off a band of pirates and
stole their ship, becoming its new
captain.
Oh, Mama is so proud of you, baby girl.
So, what do we do now? What else? We
find a town, get some food, and hitch a
ride back to Ponyville.
>> And we thank the Lord for getting us
this far in good health.
>> Hey, girls, look at that.
Damn, check that out. Oh, wow. It's
beautiful.
>> Simply marvelous, darling.
>> You know what, ladies? Maybe the weekend
didn't turn out so bad after all if we
got to be blessed with a glorious view
such as this.
>> And [__] will say, "God isn't real."
Can I get a Hmon?
>> Amen.
>> Amen. Amen.
>> You two can't say it because you're gay.
I'm going to say this one more time.
Please do. I enjoy hearing you tell me
I'm making a terrible decision. Just
saying. Bringing someone back from the
dead. Well, it's not a normal thing to
do. And besides, I'm a mortician. It's
like the total opposite of what I
normally do.
>> Are you going to do this for me or do I
have to find somebody else?
>> Fine. Fine. I'll do it. But can you at
least tell me why? My mom. It's what she
would have wanted. He may have treated
me like [__] but now that I know what I
know, I can't leave things as they are
now. Whatever. Go. Spell that creates a
portal to hell.
>> Where the hell am I?
>> Cemetery.
>> I know. I'm in a cemetery. I mean, why
am I here? What happened to the burning
pits of the aby?
>> Starlight, you idiot. You aged him down,
too. I brought him back how he looked in
the memories. That was the only
reference point I had. My dad died when
he was like 50. You [__] You
rewarded him with a spunky youthful
body.
>> Wait, who are you?
>> You don't recognize me?
>> Should I?
>> It's me, Marionette.
>> Marionette as in my marionette? You got
tall.
>> That's usually what happens when one
grows up.
Wait, that mask? You were wearing that
when you killed me.
>> Well, technically Trixie killed you. I
only led her to you.
>> Why are you still wearing that thing?
Oh, god. What happened to you?
>> I got burned.
>> I can see that.
>> Then you have your answer.
>> [__] I mean, does it hurt?
>> I've accepted who I am. I haven't seen
you in so long. And now I'm standing
here looking at you after all these
years. And I feel like all I see is a
total stranger.
You hid my sister from me. You hid my
mother from me. You made me feel like
you never wanted me. And you barely even
recognize me now. What are we if not
strangers?
>> You're not going to forgive me, are you?
No, but I understand now. I understand
why I hate you.
>> I'm uh I'm just going to go.
>> How are you feeling?
>> Forget about it. It's not important.
Hey, my mom's grave is around here
somewhere. Do you want to see it?
>> Maybe. I would love to.
>> Sweet. I always keep it pretty clean.
Let's go look for it.
Oh [__]
>> Oh, actually I think I saw it over that
way on the way in. You sure? I really
thought it was over here somewhere.
>> Well, let's go look over there anyway.
>> See her beautiful hair.
Heat. Heat. Heat.
Heat. Heat.
Heat.
me.
Let me open your eyes.